Let me take a picture of you.
I think you look so beautiful like this.
Thank you, you are also very beautiful.
Such beautiful hair strands.
This shot looks really good
What are you going to do?
Make French toast.
It's very simple.
Try it
This smells so good
It really is fragrant
Actually, it's not difficult at all
So delicious
Why is it so delicious?
Really?
You're being too kind
The last time I ate this was over twenty years ago
My mom made it for me
Withdraw
Look, Hou Chengjie is practicing over there
Oh no, I feel guilty eating this
A bit sinful
These headphones are great, they don't fall off no matter how I move.
So disciplined.
Come on, hurry.
It's blinding me.
This is free to watch.
No.
Can you guide me later?
Sure.
I want to practice.
Okay.
That.
There's actually a part of it inside.
That solves this kind of problem.
But I did that over ten years ago.
Suddenly, I can't hear anything else.
So shallow
No
This friend
Now it might just be you
Haven't seen this scene before
This is free to watch
Super Saiyan
Are you there? I'll take a look
Take a look
Yes, actually I want to go too
I was just too embarrassed to go alone
This is something I can watch for free
Too exaggerated, teacher
Too exaggerated
You must be often watched like this
You blocked very well
I can't see anything
Can't see anything
What does it look like
Do you two like sports
Yes, we do
Liking is one thing
Doing it is another
Then we can arrange to go for a run another day
When you eat later
Will you still wear a coat
No, I'm really teasing you
It's okay, no rush
Because actually over there
There's nothing to eat now
Then prepare some for me
Got it, what do you want to eat
I'll eat whatever you make.
It's heated up, teacher.
I took on a great task.
Teacher, it's heated up.
Liang Tian is such a third wheel.
Liang Tian is extremely happy.
I don't even know what she's so happy about.
Get busy
Is happiness that simple?
Can I lend a hand?
Let me
If you eat that, you're helping
No
I have a new task now
I need to make something
Look how enthusiastic Wowo (Ren Jiabi) is
How about helping me make a yogurt bowl?
Sure
Pour some yogurt and some cereal
Then cut some fruit
The fruit needs to be washed and cut
Please
This is making you anxious
You need to hurry up a bit more
You need to get on the roof
Exactly
The whole body
It's all not working
A person so cold
What do you want to do
I laughed at myself, it's really ridiculous
I'll make breakfast for everyone
No need
It's not necessary
Just do it
Just do what you need to do
It's not necessary
Getting excited, starting
Go, hurry up
No
This seems a bit too ridiculous
Actually, it's not
I'm actually not like this
But this meal you should make, you have to make it
I'm telling you
Okay, I'll do it
Words once spoken are like water spilled
Yes
Then I'll make one first
I just
Love breakfast
There's breakfast
Aren't you going to try it?
It's quite healthy
Who made this?
It must have been made by the person who assigned the task
If we go shopping later
let's bring two more friends
Are you cooking tonight?
Yes
Whatever you want to cook, I'll help you
Okay
Should we
go shopping together later?
If you have time
I'm in
Okay
If we go shopping
let's bring two more friends
Okay
More shopping?
No need, right?
You can still shop
We're shopping for some furniture, right?
The fridge is already full
Who else wants to go?
Su Yonghao, do you want to go?
Sure, let's go for a walk
Any other friends want to go?
There's one more spot
I've watched it twice
Do you want to go?
I have to work later
Then the three of us will go
Okay
So are you making fried rice tonight?
Anything is fine
That's impressive
Tell me what you want to eat first
I wonder, can you make soup?
Do you want to drink soup?
Because I have to work later
Working all afternoon might be a bit tiring
I might want to have some soup in the evening
Okay
If it's convenient
Sure
I'll go upstairs and put on a jacket
Okay
We'll leave at four o'clock
I'll go upstairs and work for a bit
I'll probably come down around dinner time
Thank you, sorry for the trouble
That's very thoughtful
Let's go
I am your guide for today
We are accompanying a distinguished leader
We went out
Drive carefully
Xiao Hou
That person
Local guide, I am the local guide
Xiao Su
Hello, leader
Wait a moment
Leader, arrange the drinks
Arrange the drinks for the evening
Strawberry juice, right?
Strawberry juice, coconut juice
I think you need to help me
Complete a main task
Which is making soup
Because I have never made soup before
No problem
We can do anything.
Just call us, and we'll help you.
Yes.
Sure.
It can't be Luo Junfan, right?
Such a melodious voice.
No.
He saw Kaka (Zheng Weiying) with
Xiao Su (Su Yonghao) playing the piano yesterday.
He's practicing by himself today.
Do you want to play something?
Or do you want to watch a movie?
Watching a movie is also good.
Or we could go to the small house across the street.
But let's go during the day.
Isn't it better to go at night?
But during the day,
it's not as cold.
But it's not as cold.
Let's go see.
Okay.
No, that's not it.
Suddenly, I don't feel like playing.
No Kaka (Zheng Weiying)
Instantly, I don't feel like playing.
Do you want to go across?
Let's explore a bit.
Let's put on some clothes.
We need to go up.
Maybe the platform on the second floor at this time.
Might be prettier.
Let's go up.
Coming up was the right choice. Look, bro.
It's very vast.
So beautiful
This is the best viewing spot
See if this angle looks good
Such beautiful people
Let's do one together.
I'll help you take the picture.
Come on.
This scene looks amazing.
This is already
I think this one is really good.
You two took this shot
It still has to be you two
Let's all thank Brother Zhang (Zhang Chenxi)
Brother Zhang gave us a hand
Great, there's a sunset
And it's right between the three towers
It looks great, I'll take a few pictures for you
Then I'll face the sunlight
It looks good no matter how you take it
You pose really well
You're really good at taking pictures
It's possible
It's beautiful
He's been praising
Because it's rare to have such an opportunity
To get to know Liang Tian better
So I took this opportunity to get to know
Hurry up and catch up
Handsome side profile
Going to eat the sun
Eat the sun
That's so funny
So cute
Really good at taking pictures
The procurement team really is
Didn't see this sunset
Such a pity
So touching
Cried
Go home
What are the folks at home doing?
I wanted to ask the same question
Probably watching a movie
Maybe
You guys are back
Look, Teacher Luo is jogging over, it's settled
I bought brown sugar, you can make a drink
Great
I feel like my stomach will hurt soon
Sit down for a bit
Just watch us work from a distance
Watch you work from a distance
Watch you work with peace of mind
This is an opportunity. Hurry!
Do you need hot water?
It seems we are a step too late.
It's already being poured over there.
Brother Su got there first.
Thank you
This is so interesting
Do you want a drink?
The yuzu tea is sweet.
Just add it in here.
If it's not flavorful enough, you can add more.
Just a little bit for me.
Thank you.
Do you still need hot water?
Thank you
It's okay, no need for such a big gesture
Teacher Luo still doesn't know what's going on.
And do you still want honey water?
It's okay.
Pour warm water. I'll pour her some cold water.
It might be a bit hot
Be careful
It's okay
Great
Teacher Luo has already started to busy himself aimlessly
Exactly
He has nothing to do now
He has lost his goal
Okay
What else needs to be added to this soup?
What else?
Wait, let the meat stew a bit more tender first
Then add it
Okay
Is it over?
It's over
It's starting now
You look a bit like Jiang Shuying with glasses.
Yes, she has a very Jiang Shuying vibe.
Someone has mentioned it before.
Do you need to take anything?
Actually, no.
You ordered it.
Thank you.
Place this main dish in the center.
He watched her drink the soup
and smiled a little
This soup is so comforting.
Your smile is reaching your ears.
Caught a fish with an upturned mouth.
You really are
Why did you put the bowl here?
Is it so natural?
No
I swear to heaven
I really didn't mean for you to serve me.
I was just standing in line here.
Understood
You could have just taken it directly.
You still need to explain.
Just kidding
Wowo (Ren Jiabi)
Your hair is really nice.
I have a secret weapon.
Let me see
This is L'Oreal's small golden bottle hair oil.
Usually, when your hair is half dry,
Just pump one or two times like this.
How is it?
It's really smooth and not frizzy anymore.
And it's very shiny.
Where is it warm?
The media room?
So sad.
You can tell that before,
when choosing breakfast, I would also prefer
I might want to choose Su Yonghao.
But after that day,
I had a good chat with him (Luo Junfan).
I had a good chat with Luo Junfan.
And then the next two days,
I started talking to him (Luo Junfan).
I think I can be firm now.
I don't know why I
get so excited so quickly.
But it seems
You could, you could have been firm.
Yes, I could have been firm.
Teacher Luo, right?
Yes.
I got excited.
Got excited.
Then,
I didn't expect on the day I chose the date,
that
you could gracefully say you can accept it.
You can understand, right?
Everyone is.
Yes.
But you will feel bad inside.
Yes
It was too sudden, mainly because
It's still very sad
But actually, I think it's too early for this
That's indeed the case
But I really am
I'm not saying it's too early for you to be affected
What I'm saying is
It's too early to draw conclusions
You can be sad
But I'm telling you this
I hope you see this point
Then you'll realize that many things
can turn around
And in the coming days
maybe during this process
your feelings might change
You might say
I don't care, it's fine
or say this is how it should be
It's the dignity of an adult
Who wouldn't want to be chosen with such determination
But I really think
This idea is too naive
There is someone
If they are truly determined and passionate
Then surely
Then surely it is
I think girls find it hard to resist
But what can you do, it's just
In relationships, you have to be prepared to get hurt
If you dare to show your heart
It's quite rare
Then I might be
The extremely passive type
If I can't see this guy's
Clear intentions
I would just watch
Him choose someone else, it doesn't matter
Would you really just watch him?
I think Xia Xia (Xia Mengting)
was definitely encouraged by her
Soul sent a message
Third date rules
The first time I was blindfolded
I wasn't chosen that time either
If I don't get invited this time
I might still have some
areas where I didn't do well
I can't concentrate on reading
No one will come today
I am already prepared
to stay at home
This part is too cruel
For me
I came to the cabin
I actually did a lot of work
I have prepared everything
Prepared to stay here for a month
If I only stay for three days
I am
Possibly the first to be eliminated in history
Male guest on a dating show
Really beautiful
Beautiful, so beautiful
Okay, next
It's our Soul sincere moment in every episode
What we just saw was
The third date released by the cabin
Called the knock invitation
What we need to guess is
How many groups will succeed in the knock invitation
The person who answers the most can hang the lock
This is so difficult
Global beauty and health products
Search Watsons mini program on WeChat
Delivered in as fast as 30 minutes
Please watch Watsons sincere reasoning moment
I have a hexagonal love here
Sorry
You can't
You can only be one-on-one
I'll think about it again
Participating offline for the first time
Still a bit nervous
We haven't matched online
Anyway, whatever you choose
We'll choose the opposite
Right
Come on, ready?
Ready
Come on, reveal the question board
Mr. Du speaks first
All four pairs are successful
I think there should be four pairs that can succeed
But I divided them into two camps
Very optimistic
Because there are two pairs
They might be mutual
Wowo (Ren Jiabi) and Xiao Jie (Hou Chengjie)
Yes, everyone should be in this group
Then Liang Tian and Hu Yunting
They should be able to match each other's intentions
I came up with one
Currently, a new choice is Liang Tian's choice
What cannot be denied is
That Xiao Hu was particularly excellent that day
But Mr. Su's previous interaction with Liang Tian was also good
They are not just building castles in the air
He still has a certain foundation
What I am most certain about
Is the pair of Liang Tian and Xiao Hu (Hu Yunting)
After you said that
I have firmed up my own choice
Wasn't your choice Su Yonghao?
Yes.
So he went the other way.
It's over
Then I'm done for
I would think
Although Xiao Hu (Hu Yunting)'s
last tardiness
was very beneficial
but I always feel that the two of them together
are not as comfortable as with Su Yonghao
it's just so natural
I was convinced
You were convinced
I want to follow your vote
Change it or not
Let's change it
Can't change it, forget it
Also
Kaka (Zheng Weiying) might choose Su Yonghao
Su Yonghao won't reject her
Yes
I think Kaka (Zheng Weiying) and Zhang Chenxi
feel pretty good together
I agree too
I think
Kaka (Zheng Weiying) won't knock on Chenxi's door
I think Kaka (Zheng Weiying) will go
knock on Su Yonghao's door
then Su Yonghao will reject her and wait for Liang Tian
so the three of them will be left alone
I'm so amazing
You're so amazing
Yes
I don't know either
I often analyze randomly
It's okay
Xia Xia (Xia Mengting) might choose an older brother
Then choose this Chenxi
Then Mr. Luo will be left alone
I think Xia Mengting
will still knock on Luo Junfan's door
I would think
if Xia Mengting knocks on his door again
if he refuses again
he really is
a child
Yes
if he refuses again
he's being too much
Mr. Xu, I have another perspective to offer you
Actually, many boys are directive animals
What kind of animals?
Most boys are directive animals
It's like he received a message
saying that she wasn't interested in me
and the photo she posted was suggestive
with another boy's photo
but after he received that message
I think with Mr. Luo's
usual headstrong personality
he might say to think about someone else
Yes
I also think
Xia Xia (Xia Mengting) should go
and knock on Mr. Luo's door again
But I think
Mr. Luo will refuse
Yes, I agree
Yes
Okay
Use the Soul APP
Meet interesting souls who understand you
Next, we enter the Soul's true reveal moment
She is the first one
Still a bit conflicted
Maybe Hu Yunting and Su Yonghao
They will take better care of me.
After leaving, it's still Hu Yunting.
Torn between Su Yonghao and him.
But she mentioned Xiao Hu (Hu Yunting) first.
Hello
Arrived at the last moment
I thought no one would come
Your hand is all red
It's okay
(Room) so close
It's so difficult, really very difficult.
It's too difficult.
But she came back again
Came back again
Really
This heartbeat is really
She stopped, she's leaving
What zodiac sign are you?
Snake
Look at this
Is this us?
This is a snake
It's even wearing a hat
It's waiting for us
Always looking forward to being with you
Looking forward to the date
Really
Whose door is this?
Can't tell right now.
This is Su Yonghao's door.
Xiao Hu's (Hu Yunting's) door.
Su Yonghao's.
Look, look.
But there is.
That cut, it's cut towards.
Wait a moment.
I really can't take it anymore.
Xiao Su (Su Yonghao)
Who
That Xiao Hu (Hu Yunting)
Chose Hu Yunting
Hu Yunting
What I want to say is
It seems like we've had a lot of fate these past few days
And a lot of opportunities
And I feel very happy being with you
I feel very comfortable too
Me too
But do you remember the two of us
On the day we went to Cyber Jump
We said in the car
It seems like the days we've been here are still very short
And we also want to interact more with everyone and see
Then
I just knocked on Su Yonghao's door
We were wrong
It's already done, already
Your editing is really
I am so angry
Your editing really makes me angry
Then I just knocked on Su Yonghao's door
So happy
I just feel that these past few days in the cabin
It seems like we haven't really talked alone before.
Because you are always taking care of everyone.
It seems like you were always in the crowd
I just think on the first day
our meeting was a bit brief
Yes
I have thought about it myself
If there is a one-on-one opportunity
I just want to talk to you again
To get to know you better
Because we have known each other for a very short time
And we have been in close contact
Without one-on-one
This is quite delicious
I'm back
What
Give her something personal
Bought some food for you
Dried strawberries
Thank you
I know you bought this especially for me
And then I
Do you agree
Of course
Laughing like this
Sure
I am also looking forward to our date
I also have many questions to ask you
Sure
See you tomorrow
Rest early
Su Yonghao is smiling so happily
No time
To have a one-on-one opportunity with Su Yonghao
So I think I need a chance
To have a one-on-one chat with Su Yonghao
To understand this person
And to answer some of my doubts
So I need to be very honest with you
I just feel
Like I need to create some opportunities
To talk to others
Maybe get to know everyone better
But I feel I must be honest with you
Thank you for telling me
Actually
Because everyone is really excellent
It feels like if a decision is made too early
Both sides will feel pressured
And it will also sacrifice our
Opportunities to experience and get to know people
Yes
Everyone is trying to say something
They don't want to say
So
So thank you very much
For telling me this today
You gave me a chance to
Respond to what I want to say
Have fun
Okay
You too
Good night
Thank you
Liang Tian did a pretty good job.
Yes, it's quite heartwarming.
Yes.
Just don't let people hold onto empty fantasies.
When I heard her knock on the door,
seeing her made me very happy.
When she said those words,
my feelings were a bit complicated.
So I think,
we should each go
and interact with the people we want to know.
After more interactions,
if I still have the chance later,
we can go on a date again.
We will be more certain about our relationship
and feelings.
Xia Xia (Xia Mengting)
It feels like Xia Xia (Xia Mengting) has lost weight
The order of appearance is very important
My car was about to leave when he arrived
Who doesn't want to be chosen firmly?
If I went to find you first
Then went to find her
There would be enough time
But personally
I really want to understand her as a person
If I can't see this guy
Clearly expressing his feelings
I would just watch
Him choose someone else
It doesn't matter anymore
Would you really just watch him?
He scared me when he came back
He is
back
Brother, are you eating?
Not eating
I asked if you were interested
It's nothing, I don't want to talk
Yesterday, Liang Tian told me he didn't even have dinner
Yeah, he couldn't swallow
Gone
There were some regrets yesterday
Then I want to say
If today
There is such an opportunity
I want to tell him
Don't blame yourself for yesterday's events
Feel guilty
This should be Luo Junfan's door
Yes, she said not to let him feel guilty
I also want
To take this opportunity to tell him my feelings
Hello
I'm so nervous
My heart is beating so fast
I
I'm really sorry about yesterday
It's okay
I think it's just
You also need to be firmly chosen
So, shall we go on a date tomorrow?
That sentence is too powerful
Yeah, I also think she will
It really seems a bit irresistible
She's really nice
So, shall we go on a date tomorrow?
I didn't expect you to come.
What?
Why?
In the few days I've been in the cabin
I have experienced
For example, feeling happy
Yesterday, my emotions were really out of control
I was a bit scared by myself
Yesterday, I felt very guilty
I didn't even know how to talk to you
Then I felt
I am actually a person who
One day is not enough for me to adjust
I hope I can calm down by myself
So I want to think it through myself
What do I really want
Then
So you missed my date
And you want to refuse my date again
How can you bear it
Let's sit down and talk about this tomorrow
I think so.
Good, very good.
I'm sorry.
You're confused
I'm so angry
I don't really understand
why I received such a response
Actually, when I went to find him
I didn't expect him to reject me
because he clearly said yesterday
that he felt guilty towards me
and his overall state was very poor
I want to say
if I give him a chance at this moment
to not feel so awkward and self-blaming
shouldn't he seize it
he actually rejected me
I am really very confused
I think it's very cruel
I think this is deeply hurting her
That feeling, I think
is no better than standing there yesterday
While I was waiting,
I was still very nervous.
If no one knocks on the door tonight,
I will be eliminated.
I will be eliminated tonight.
Has it been three days already?
Regarding Hou Chengjie, I am actually curious about his inner world
I am also a bit curious
About people like him
What their inner world is like
Hu Yunting, I really don't understand him well
Maybe because he speaks very little
So I feel unclear
So I originally wanted
To have a chance to understand him better
Su Yonghao is definitely my first choice
But Hou Chengjie seems to have said
he came for me
So, do I need to respond
to his
so-called feeling of coming for me
I have been torn between Hou Chengjie and Su Yonghao
for a long time.
Extremely nervous
It's like waiting for the competition results
Waiting for the exam results
This kind of feeling
Heart rate rapidly soaring to over two hundred
Wowo (Ren Jiabi)
So nervous
Hurry up, it's too nerve-wracking.
Fast forward, I can't stand it.
Hello.
Who is it?
Really.
That.
Would you like to go on a date with me tomorrow?
Sorry
Okay
I'm heading back now
Sorry
It's okay
Goodbye
But he refused
He refused
He's just waiting for Wowo (Ren Jiabi)
Even if Wowo (Ren Jiabi) doesn't come
He doesn't need to stay in this small room
Yes, he's definitely waiting for Wowo (Ren Jiabi)
I didn't accept Zheng Weiying's invitation
My first instinct was
I still wanted to go and meet Ren Jiabi
and interact a bit more
Although I might also face a
risk of leaving
but I also want to be true to myself
and confront my most genuine feelings
It's better to die standing than to live on your knees.
If Wowo (Ren Jiabi) doesn't choose him, he will leave.
He would rather leave, but he will wait for Wowo (Ren Jiabi).
Risking elimination.
Yes, this is quite touching.
Hello
Great
I see your expression
What's wrong with my expression?
I see your expression, do you have a date?
I'm here
Waiting for you
Really?
Really
Then let's go out on a date tomorrow and have some fun
Okay
When I opened the door
and saw it was Ren Jiabi
I was a bit stunned
I didn't expect it to really be her
That date
and when I saw her wearing glasses yesterday
I think she is a
very pure and clean person
with a childlike personality
I think this purity and cleanliness is actually
a rare quality in adults nowadays
I am a rather pessimistic person
I don't really believe the best choice will appear
in my life
The person I chose happened to choose me too
It's quite touching
Yes, determined
Really determined
See you tomorrow
Okay
Okay, goodbye
Goodbye
My heart is racing
We are so happy too
Awesome
I am really looking forward to my date with Ren Jiabi
because I haven't had the chance
to have a good conversation with her
I actually hope
I can have a good chat with her
Watching Three Kingdoms
Went to watch "Romance of the Three Kingdoms"
When Hou Chengjie rejected me
It felt like a weight was lifted
I just want to say
Sometimes it might still give
Still give myself some shackles
I would feel
He seemed to say he came for me
Then I might need to respond
This kind of
So-called feeling of coming for me
Even if things go well between us later
Or don't go well
It's my own choice
Not being swept away by this feeling
So I am very grateful
For his rejection this time
His rejection this time for me
Will ease the shackles in my heart
He should give up, right?
Isn't he supposed to calm down?
Yes
No
He went out to get some fresh air to calm down
Going out for an appointment
Who is he meeting?
Senior Sister
He still invited Liang Tian
Tomorrow, you
I want to invite you on a date
Have you already made the arrangements?
Didn't he need to calm down?
Yes.
He is just very conflicted.
He is extremely conflicted.
Can I say a few words first?
Go ahead.
Then you can speak.
Like this.
We don't have much interaction.
Why do I have such a good impression?
You did things I didn't dare to do.
So I feel deep down that
we are the same kind of people.
I can't help but pay attention to you.
This is beyond my control.
You might already have a date tomorrow
Or you might say no
But I think I will talk to you
And it's great to speak casually
To be honest
I think you are a very genuine person
Sometimes I think your way of expressing
Is something I should learn
I think it's really good
Very sincere
Do you understand?
Yes, I think it will be much easier this way
You know I hesitated a lot yesterday
I made a big mistake
I heard about it
I don't know if this is right
But at least that's how I feel right now
Yes
That's it
I honestly tell you
I will refuse
Will refuse
Thank you, junior brother
I think
No, I think you are very
Being direct is good for me
This way I won't overthink
Then you should sleep
Thank you
Goodbye
Salute
He is actually very chaotic.
He himself is very chaotic.
He is a bit twisted.
Yes.
Very twisted.
A bit twisted.
He shouldn't have left this door.
Actually, when I came back at that time
I was very happy
I felt a sense of calm
So I will still say
I once had feelings for her
or this kind of affection
I don't think it's shameful
And at the same time, I think
this matter has come to an end
and it's concluded
I can handle what comes next
whatever happens
I'll just go with it
I'll definitely sleep well tonight
Good night to you
You really should go to bed
Good night, go to sleep
When it was our turn to knock on the door
At that moment, in my heart
The first person I thought of was Zheng Weiying
I knew she didn't come the first time
It meant that her first choice in the first round
was definitely not me
Even in this situation
I felt at that moment
I should still follow my heart
and choose someone
the first person I wanted to choose
He still chose Kaka (Zheng Weiying)
Is someone knocking on my door?
Brother Chen
Hello
Surprised?
Will you go on a date with me tomorrow?
Brother Chen sounded pretty cool when he said that.
Let me think about it.
She won't reject him, will she?
Okay.
Okay
Alright
Really good
Good
That's it then
So be it
Goodbye
See you tomorrow then
Bye
Brother Chen is quite good
Tomorrow will be our third date.
In my opinion, it's the second time.
It's still quite different from a one-on-one date.
So in my mind, tomorrow
might be the second real date.
I hope to get to know her better.
To help everyone better
understand the person in front of them.
Xiao Hu is still very dedicated.
Congratulations
Pretty good
He deserves it, he's so good
What's going on?
What do you mean?
What's the situation?
Open the luggage.
The luggage was just taken out.
I didn't dare to open it before.
What if we have to leave?
Be ready to leave at any time.
When I'm confused
I don't want to exhaust myself
So I went to talk to him
She went to talk to him
Do you have time? Let's talk
Sure
I want to know what they talked about
Why didn't you choose me?
Xia Xia (Xia Mengting) is really brave
To be honest
Brave, really brave
If it were me
I would have run away long ago
But bravery was misplaced
It's self-harm
Misplaced trust
Yes
They need to talk
I'll leave first
I thought they were looking for you
No
What kind of situation is this?
Actually, I wanted to talk to you first yesterday
To find you and talk first
You're wearing so little, why not wear more?
I added more clothes.
So are you going out tomorrow?
I'm not going out tomorrow.
You didn't wait for the person you wanted to wait for.
We can go and choose again later.
Go and choose again.
And then?
She asked him.
And then she was rejected.
Yes, that's right.
Okay.
She happened to be walking behind
Exactly
First, she has an invitation
Second,
She also said she just wants to be friends
There is no desire to make contact
So I think
This actually makes me feel more comfortable
Where to sit
Sit here
Up to you
I'll sit here
You sit here
Okay
Sorry
You really looked
I really
I think it's so cruel
I really think it's very cruel
Were you more guilty yesterday
Or more guilty today
I felt even more guilty yesterday
Why
Actually, at that time
When I received this (limited-time date) task
My thought was
To prioritize based on your desire to go
Over the past few days, I have been
I wanted to understand Liang Tian
But my feelings are not like that
My feeling is
From our first date to the next day
Including before going to bed the next night
The signals you gave me were mutual
So this is my problem
This is what I think
The moment I post now is
Whoever I spend more time with
I will post this
Because I think this is more
Pure
Out of respect, right?
No, not entirely
It's just that my feeling at the moment is very good
Yes
And actually, after making the flowers that day
I felt a lot more fondness for you
And actually that day
I was looking forward to seeing Liang Tian
Or Wowo (Ren Jiabi)
But we ended up having a great conversation that day
And then the next day
We were sitting there, right?
We were sitting over there, right?
And when you came over
You must have thought about it
Whether to sit with Wowo (Ren Jiabi)
Or over here
Of course, between me and Wowo (Ren Jiabi)
There wasn't much space
And then you sat down
Between the two of us
Actually, your hand would touch my shoulder
I don't know if those
Were signs of affection
Or what
The next day we were supposed to meet
I still wanted to meet you
But the order of our interactions these two days
Made me feel that my fondness
Would still be greater for Liang Tian
This is my emotional journey
I feel like right now
I haven't fully thought it through
whether I really like you
or to that extent
if I continue
it might be locked in
So now Liang Tian isn't interested in you
Yes, that's right
And then?
So for me
So it will extend to the second choice
The third choice?
No
I would feel like a backup
No, none of that
To be honest, I was really shocked.
I think you're being insincere.
Your actions and what you just said
don't quite add up.
Because the reason you just gave for rejecting me was
that you needed to calm down.
You said one day wasn't enough for you to adjust.
I'm very confused.
I don't understand.
You just have someone else you want to get to know.
You can just say it directly.
But telling me like this
makes me feel like you're lying.
You can say it directly.
This won't work.
Maybe it's too direct.
Because it would be too much.
So try to be more tactful.
It would be better.
What kind of logic is that?
Aren't you being direct now?
Why aren't you continuing to be tactful now?
Because we still have to spend a lot of time together here.
If you want to be more dignified, you can say
because we have
had several dates before.
So this time, I want to get to know different people.
I think this
won't bring me any harm.
Understood.
But I am really hurt today.
Definitely.
This is my problem.
I apologize to you.
Okay.
I'm really sorry.
So how do you think we should interact in the future?
Actually, when I was with you today,
I treated you like a friend.
You are really amazing.
You adjusted so quickly.
I don't know how you will be,
but I will still talk to you.
I will still hang out with you.
And you can reject me.
Of course, you are fine.
Yes.
I will still interact with you like today.
You are really amazing.
Maybe it's impressive.
You can curse if you want.
You're so honest.
I can be very honest with you too.
You can say it.
On the day we chose breakfast,
I thought my portion would be Su Yonghao's.
Although it wasn't Old Su (Su Yonghao),
I think you are also good.
Because you are also someone I want to know.
But unlike you,
I think our communication is very pleasant.
And very comfortable.
Plus, the last time we had a four-person date,
It happened to be two pairs.
It will subjectively
Send signals to others.
It seems like the two of us are indeed
Locked together.
Including you saying in the car,
We look at each other.
And I indeed have fewer
Opportunities to interact with other guys.
Opportunities to interact, understood.
Just like today, I indeed missed out.
Including that day's date,
Hou Chengjie, he dated all four girls.
If he didn't show up,
I am just nobody
I definitely hurt you
I definitely know this
But I am very confused right now
I just don't really know
how to face you in the future
I am also very straightforward
because I am very scared
I didn't come to talk to you about this today
Tomorrow we will probably be very awkward
So I think it is still necessary
to come and talk to you
But today I am
I am firm in my choice
Including going to find you
I also want to tell you
I said
I hope you can
know from your heart
that you are the one I firmly chose
You don't need to waver
I said I am like a kitten
When a kitten likes someone
it just wants to be by their side
just watching them from afar
Then I found that I really
my body is very honest
but I really want to be by your side
and watch you
And I also feel like
the timing of our meeting
is actually very important for both of us
It's fate
This is a kind of fate
I also want to cherish it
I personally feel comfortable
Maybe you think it's too fast
My thoughts are very simple
Not that many
I actually saw you come today
I think you are very brave
And then
I mustered up the courage
Yes
I know
You said your heart was beating fast
And to be honest
I haven't been firmly chosen by someone in a long time
It's like you said, hoping to be firmly chosen
That sentence is really touching
So at that moment, I felt
You just said, what's the big deal
But I am the kind of person
If you take one step back, I take ninety-nine steps back
I want to talk to you
Including what comes next
We can still hang out together
But I can't
At this moment, I can't accept a date
This
I'm not that carefree
I can't be so carefree
I also think a lot
But I think in the end,
you can't lie to yourself.
You also can't
I understand.
You don't need to keep emphasizing it.
It hurts my self-esteem.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, it's not that.
The reason I want to say this
is that I don't think your efforts,
your sincerity,
your courage is laughable.
You are much braver than me.
I'm not a brave person.
But I tried.
You did something very brave.
You tried your best.
You did something extremely brave.
Did he cry?
He probably won't cry.
Alright
It's fine
We are all adults
We are currently in a
phase of exploration and discovery
No one said I must have a result
I'm just very confused
Because your actions and your previous statements
are not quite the same
Understood
This is where you will see
I can understand that
Yes
Normal logical thinking
should be that you feel sorry
then you should make up for this apology
At least you should make up for this date
because you missed it
Yes, exactly
Yes
Because that was supposed to be my time
I agree you are right
This should be a better way
But at that moment I didn't
think of it
No, today this also counts
because we have talked for a long time
This can also be called a date
Then this really is
the worst date in history
It's really good
because we clearly expressed our thoughts to each other
It's rare to have such an opportunity
So I think actually
just talking to you today
I think my understanding of you
has changed again
Don't give me that
I don't want to hear this right now
Who is it?
I don't know.
I didn't see clearly, but
it feels like they are all like this.
I just told you, this is the second person.
One person came in and one left just now.
One person came in and one left.
He thinks it's hard to get close to this place.
Of course, definitely.
Who wants to come in?
Here comes another one.
Hello.
Why aren't you running away?
He wants to throw away the trash.
Tomorrow we'll be like lonely old people
Stuck in this house
It's fine
I need to be alone
I think it's fine
Okay
I've asked everything I wanted to
Let it go
The events of today
And the end of these conversations
I feel I really need
To shift my focus
It might take more time
To calm down and examine
To observe
Don't rush headlong
After I clarify things
I won't waste energy on internal conflicts
Or overthink
This is important to me
As for what comes next
I haven't thought much about it
Just let it be
I don't know what will happen in the small room
What kind of things will happen
Do you think they have the same mental journey?
Probably not
Yes
Maybe they'll all go out on dates tomorrow
So, who are you going on a date with tomorrow?
No one.
No, that's ridiculous.
Really?
It's all expected.
I'm not unhappy.
You don't need to hug me.
He won't be unhappy.
I'm not unhappy.
But I really asked him out because
I have a lot of doubts about him.
A lot of doubts.
I also have many questions to ask.
You and Xiao Hou (Hou Chengjie)
So Xiao Hou (Hou Chengjie) his task should be
He succeeded in his date
He stayed
So cruel
Yes
Although I'm happy he stayed
But how did I become a part of this game
Looks good
So exciting
This is the most exciting part
It must be Xia Xia (Xia Mengting) looking for Teacher Luo
Yes
Really didn't expect it
Everyone towards Luo Junfan
Isn't it just confusion after confusion
Actually, Luo Junfan is not a bad person.
He is actually very honest and very...
But he has some methodological errors.
The first one
At the beginning of this kind of relationship
It's important to convey information
Back then in that flower house
He was very intimate
Xia Xia (Xia Mengting) received a stronger message
Yes
Very firm
If Luo Junfan didn't do it on purpose
Then it's his way
He doesn't know how to
get along with a girl he just met
You conveyed the wrong message
Making her think
you have strong feelings for her
So that Xia Xia (Xia Mengting) entered
her own storyline
So in the end, it caused
such a misunderstanding
In this misunderstanding, you would feel
Luo Junfan would also feel wronged
But Xia Xia (Xia Mengting) feels even more wronged
From beginning to end
there's nothing to feel wronged about
He knew it would be like this
I don't really understand either
He knows the consequences of his actions
He knows everything
I'm being very cruel
I will hurt you this way
You know why you still want to do it
Yes
And the most confusing part about him
I think it's after he finishes
Did you notice
After he was rejected twice
His reaction was
Relieved
Finally rejected
He sighed in relief
Yes
Because he just briefly mentioned
his past romantic experiences
saying that I haven't been
firmly chosen by someone for a long time
so I don't know
in his past romantic experiences
what he concluded
or what kind of experiences he had
that made him feel that the moment I was rejected
was actually reassuring
Yes
I think he has a bit of that
habitual
willingness to push the responsibility onto the other person
and then feel
that he is not responsible for this matter anyway
He is in pain
But he won't admit he's in pain
He says he's fine
He felt relieved
He might be very empty inside
A person with a lot of inferiority
A bit insecure
Then Xia Xia (Xia Mengting)
Was so determined today
Said you need to be chosen firmly
Then said I need to calm down alone
I turned around and went to find Liang Tian
Yes, that was the most confusing part
He is very conflicted
He doesn't know what he wants
I'm so angry that I have a headache.
Yes, although you see Xia Xia (Xia Mengting)
She has been expressing her emotions.
But her emotions also reveal her inner self.
Actually, today as
a guy's perspective,
first of all, I saw
that some people
are naturally capable of loving others.
Some people are very good at loving others.
But some people, like Luo Junfan,
he just doesn't know how to
love others.
Or how to express
how he feels at the moment.
Whether it's feeling sorry for you
or protecting you,
it's just that
even though Luo Junfan is outstanding in his field,
he is a top performer.
But in love,
I think Xia Xia (Xia Mengting) is his teacher.
He is just a beginner.
He really needs to learn a lot.
Yes, on Luo Junfan
I think he shows a lot of
actually in society
a lack of emotional education
a very important manifestation
I don't know how to properly
appropriately and decently
express affection to a girl
Secondly, I want to take care of your self-esteem
but I still don't have the right way
to take care of a girl's self-esteem
There's a third one
Regarding the essence of love
Including within romantic relationships
Understanding some phenomena
The understanding is also limited
These few points are killing me
Of course
I think there's another issue with him
He knows that
Doing this will hurt the girl
But I'll still do it
I think actually maybe
In a relationship between two people
There should be some empathy and
Perspective-taking
Yes
Luckily, the person he met was Xia Xia (Xia Mengting)
Xia Xia (Xia Mengting) is proactive
In solving problems
She doesn't internalize
She expresses everything
She lets it all out
Then we communicate clearly
And move on
And you see Xia Xia (Xia Mengting) crying for a long time
In the end, she was the one handing tissues to Teacher Luo
That was so funny
At that moment, I
Couldn't hold back anymore
So, all the men out there
take out your notebooks and write this down
learn this, really
Of course, I think Xia Xia (Xia Mengting)
if we were to give her some advice
I think many kind-hearted girls
make the common mistake
of imagining things kindly
you'll find that encouraging her
to knock on Luo Junfan's door
she has an imagination
that part was her hearing from others
that he didn't eat yesterday
She softened her heart.
Many girls are soft-hearted.
Because they are too kind.
You will imagine some things.
This actually needs attention.
You really need to learn.
For example, from Xia Xia's (Xia Mengting's) perspective.
Everything was fine initially.
Suddenly, the other person didn't like it anymore.
She thinks this is called cliff-like ambiguity.
Cliff-like ambiguity is from...
From Xia Xia's perspective.
Cliff-like ambiguity is similar to...
What we call cliff-like breakup.
What kind of breakup is this?
It's like you're still immersed in
your own story
and the other person suddenly withdraws
without explanation
without a process of easing
This phenomenon is called cliff-edge ambiguity
We need to affirmatively say
cliff-edge ambiguity is wrong
It is quite cruel
In intimate relationships
or friendships or any other relationships
we should not leave without saying goodbye
This is indeed quite harmful
People with low self-confidence
will reflect on whether it's their own problem
How to prevent cliff-edge ambiguity, teacher
This is very difficult to prevent, right
Very difficult to prevent, right
But we need to learn to cope
If you are not lucky enough
you encounter a sudden ambiguous relationship
or a sudden breakup
what should we do
There is a way to handle this
First, you need to activate
your self-protection mechanism
when faced with a sudden ambiguous relationship
but this does not mean
I have been abandoned
Secondly, we need to clean up the battlefield
I accept this reality, alright
then I will withdraw
I will also withdraw
So, like Xia Xia (Xia Mengting)
she withdrew quite quickly
She said she would take ninety-nine steps back
Yes
Because if you continue with him
your harm will be greater later
such experts can only match with experts
if you are not such a person
just run quickly
yes, the faster you run, the better
clean up this battlefield
as clean as possible
it's just a short pain
it's just a short pain, yes
then let's announce the results
come, let's see what the results are
It seems like Sis Yixin got everything right.
Sis Yixin got everything right.
Yes.
You hit three
There's a boomerang
That's amazing
Padlock
Come, padlock
The first lock of the season
was hard-earned
This is you
earned with your clever little brain
Luck
Awesome
Interesting souls meet freely
This show is sponsored by the app that young people are using
Soul APP
Exclusively titled broadcast
Global beauty and health products
On the Watsons mini program
Thanks to the beauty of health and the health of beauty
Jointly sponsored by Watsons
Okay
How will the three groups proceed
with their exclusive two-person dates
Let's take a look together
So cool
I'm really looking forward to
getting to know you
I think it's not just about talking about life
but also about discussing things we like
The atmosphere is just right
This day
is the happiest day I've had so far
Ready, go
Yes, really
Hold onto me
I'm protecting you
Perfect
I'm very curious where everyone went today
Still curious
Smells good
It's ready to eat
This soup is so delicious
When I originally made this beef noodle soup
I hoped Liang Tian could eat it
Xiao Hu (Hu Yunting) is heartbroken
So pitiful
I'll have another bowl
Soul sent a message
I just wrote a short essay
Short essay
I really want to tell someone
He was very direct and firm
And in front of everyone
I just want to ask you one question
Would you be willing to
Take a step forward
What kind of scene is this
Is Wo Wo crying
I just wanted to say
I sent you the exact same words
Your birthday is quite a coincidence
It's just one day away from Children's Day
Big friend
Although not a little kid
But a big friend
I think after talking about the pressure
everyone feels better
I have a feeling that
after I talked about it yesterday
I felt much more relieved
You should be firm
I am very firm
Especially after tonight, I am even more firm
Everyone
Old Hu, cover for me
Cover for me
Subtitles team, add a drumstick
So sweet
You understand me
So this is what other people's dates are like
This is too happy
You must have been overjoyed at that time
You should show it
Victory and defeat are common in war
Will support like this
I was really immature